MANUEL LÓPEZ JOVÉ

WEB DEVELOPER

🖂 liaimasoft@gmail.com 🔌 299-4643957

O Viedma - Río Negro

LinkedIn: in/manuel-lopez-jove/

Portfolio: https://liaima.ar

GitHub: /liaima

GitLab: /liaimasoft

SUMARY

Web developer with more than two years of experience specializing in PHP as the main language. Passionate about continuous learning and professional growth in constant search for new opportunities to improve my skills and stay updated on the latest web development technologies,

WORK EXPERIENCE

Desarrollador Web Freelance

PatagoniaDev - Viedma RN

September 2023 ~ Now

Tasks:

On-demand development of tasks for client systems in Python and JS

Stack:

Python 3 | Django 4.2.8 | JQuery | Docker | Postgres 15.2

PHP Developer

Ministerio de Salud (Minstery of Helth) de Río Negro - Viedma RN

April 2022 ~ Now

Tasks

Maintenance and development of the SIGEP system for the administration of beneficiaries, benefits, and billing of hospitals adhered to the SUMAR program of the Province of Rio Negro Argentina

Stack:

PHP 5.6 | Yii 1.1 | JQuery | Docker | Postgres 13

Web Developer

Universidad Nacional del Comahue - CURZA - Viedma RN

Octover 2021 ~ March 2024

Development of systems for internal use of the Regional Center and the University and maintenance of existing developments and website

Stack:

PHP 8.0 | Yii 2 | React 16.8.6 | JQuery | Docker | Postgres 14.2

App Developer

Cabalgatas El Tero - Villa la Angostura NQN

Octubre 2021 ~ Diciembre 2021

Tasks:

Development of an application to manage reservations according to the needs of the company

Repository Git: https://github.com/liaima/cabalgatasElTero

Stack:

PHP 8.0 | Yii2 | Docker | MySql 5.7.27

REFERENCES

available upon request

EDUCATION

Degree: University technician in web development | Universidad Nacional del Comahue

Languages:

English: Intermediate B1 Japanese: Basic

EXPERIENCE ABROAD:

Student exchange to Japan with AES scholarship

(11months, 2009)